[birds chirping]
Oh, Pascal, it would've been so great
to have one of these
when I was locked up in that tower.
[chuckling]
-Oh, so cute! Aw.
-[cooing]
Whoa, that doesn't look good.
[chuckles nervously]
Dark, ominous clouds usually make me think
something villainous is afoot.
Oh! It's just a little bit of rain.
Aw, but the bunnies are all getting wet.
And the birds.
[gasps] And that itty-bitty ant.
Pascal, all these poor little critters
are out there in the rain.
[thunder rumbling]
[mumbles indistinctly]
[sighs] I know the ocean is my friend,
but I do like being nice and dry inside.
I used to want to escape the palace,
but not on a day like this.
[thunder crashes]
[sighs] I think it's perfect weather
for a quiet day--
[caws loudly]
-Inside.
-Sorry, he's--
-[Heihei caws]
-Heihei.
-[all chuckling]
-Technically, under the sea,
every day is a rainy one.
Such a downpour!
I hope the animals
can stay warm and dry out there.
It feels like I should be helping them.
Don't feel too bad.
Wild animals don't mind a passing storm.
They'll make the most of the day.
And so will we.
I, for one, am happy to relax
and enjoy a cozy afternoon indoors.
[chuckles]
Some relax with card games,
others relax with chaos!
[chuckles] Let's see how relaxing this is.
-[thunder crashes]
-[Cheshire Cat chuckles]
Your turn, Ariel.
[gasps] Two geese.
-Go fish!
-No, um...
Oh! [chuckles] Don't mind us, dearies.
Just looking for the bathtub!
-[geese laughing]
-Uh, it's that way.
-[both] Thank you!
-These accommodations are simply divine.
So divine.
Uh, we all saw that, right?
The only special ingredient
I put in the tea was love, I promise.
What is going on?
-Huh?
-Whoa.
[mumbling indistinctly, groans]
[piano playing]
[Heihei screeches]
[chirps]
Where are these animals coming from?
Huh. Maybe they did mind the storm.
There must be a window or door
open somewhere.
Let's split up and investigate.
[all grunt]
Cozy afternoon, indeed! [chuckles]
[thunder crashes]
[gasps, grunts]
How do these bunnies keep multiplying?
Hey! Stop that.
-[objects clattering]
-[gasps]
[grunts]
[gasps]
-[growls]
-Oh, would you like a--
-Pie? [chuckles nervously]
-[grunts]
-I don't hear anything, do you?
-[trills]
-[birds chirping]
-[gasps] Ooh!
[chuckles]
Whoa! [chuckles]
-[birds screeching]
-Whoa! [screams, grunts]
The dining room's secure. [gasps] Huh.
[monkeys screeching]
I take that back.
The dining room is definitely not secure.
[grunts]
-[Heihei clucks]
-[Moana shushes]
-[thunder crashes]
-[Moana yelps]
[snakes hissing]
[Kaa] Oh. [chuckles]
Would you like to...
join us? [hisses]
Join you.
[screams]
[gasps] No!
Nope. Nope, nope, nope, nope, nope!
[hissing]
[panting]
Dolphins? In the fountain?
-[Cheshire Cat laughs]
-[dolphins clicking]
[Founder] Help!
Ariel! Help! Ariel!
Flounder! [grunts]
Flounder, where are you?
Whoa, whoa! [yelling] Ariel!
[gasps]
[Flounder panting]
[yells]
[panting]
[grunting]
Uh...
[screaming]
-[screaming continues]
-[Ariel] Come with me!
Oh! Thanks!
[panting]
-[grunts]
-[Flunder yelling]
[growls]
[crunch]
[Ariel chuckles]
-[Flunder screams]
-[Ariel grunts]
Ariel!
[gasps]
[dolphins clicking]
Ugh! [spits, sighs] Thanks!
Hm. Hm.
[Jasmine] [panting] Are they gone?
There aren't any bears behind me,
are there?
-[Jasmine yelps]
-[Moana screams]
-[both screaming]
-[Heihei clucks]
[Mulan] Let me guess.
Did everyone else stumble upon
a bunch of animals in the castle?
The kitchen certainly isn't lacking
any bare necessities.
Was the upstairs clear, Moana?
No, no!
Nope-ity, nope, nope, nope, nope, nope.
Would anyone happen to have
a better Flounder-holder?
[monkeys screeching]
Thank you. Next question.
Has anyone seen Rapunzel?
[Rapunzel screaming]
[screaming continues, grunts]
-Oh, no!
-Ugh!
How did all these animals
get inside the castle?
[coughing]
Every window and door is shut.
Hm. I bet they have the answer.
[Mulan and Jasmine] Hm.
Follow that ant trail!
[Beaver] Eh, let's see here...
[grunting] This is...
heavier than it looks.
You're building a dam indoors?
Well, uh, safety first, sonny!
You never know
when water will come a-rushin'!
Gotta get these logs movin'!
Water indoors?
I didn't even know that could happen.
Finally, someone understands
the importance of indoor damming.
[chuckling] Oh! Now, that's a stick!
[groans] Amelia, if I walk much farther,
I'll get flat feet.
Now, don't you start
with that again, Abigail. [gasps]
Oh. Oh, my. There must be some big event
going on down the hall.
[gasps] Oh, fancy that.
We must get tickets.
Oh, indeed! [chuckles]
[Mulan panting]
The ants are coming from inside this room!
Let's go!
-[animal sounds]
-[Mulan gasps]
Oh, thank goodness! [chuckling]
You're all here!
Animals just keep coming through.
[gasps] I'm exposed!
They are coming into the castle
through Wardrobe's portal!
-Quick! Let's help Wardrobe!
-[chuckling]
[gasps, yells]
Whoa!
[growling]
Uh...
-[monkeys chattering]
-[Rapunzel grunts]
Oh.
[Ariel grunts]
[Flounder groans]
[panting]
[grunts] Whoa!
[bears growling]
[panting]
Nope!
-[Rapunzel grunts]
-[Wardrobe yelps]
[grunts]
Phew! Sure glad that's over.
-That was neat!
-[Moana chuckles]
Now we can get these animals home safely.
And get back to our card game.
I had a winning hand.
Um, Wardrobe, why are you pink?
Whoa. You'd be pink, too, if you had
this many critters in your drawers!
-No, this pink seems...
-[Cheshire Cat chuckles]
Enchanted.
Oh, dear, that can't be good.
[gasps] Oh! Whoa!
-[neighing]
-[monkeys chattering]
[growling]
Where are the animals going?
I mean, animals always flee
when they sense danger.
-[rumbling]
-Look out, everyone!
-This armoire's gonna blow!
-[elephants trumpeting]
Oh, dear!
[grunts]
Stampede!
[trumpeting]
[grunts]
Uh, Ariel? [grunts]
-May I?
-Of course! Thanks for asking.
I'll always save your tail.
-[elephants trumpeting]
-[Mulan panting]
[grunts]
Heads up, Moana!
[grunting]
[yelps]
[grunts] Let's lead them outside!
[trumpeting]
How do you steer these things?
[elephants trumpeting]
[Mulan] Hold on, everyone!
This way. Huh?
Huh. Oh, no, we're not going to fit!
-[animal sounds]
-[Amelia] Oh, dear.
It must be intermission!
Well, that was rather quick!
Oh, excuse me, madam.
May I ask how you're enjoying the show?
[elephants trumpeting]
My dam!
Ah, I didn't account for pachyderms!
[grunts]
[crashing]
[animal sounds]
[groans] This was supposed to be
a relaxing day!
This is not the face of a person relaxed!
It could be worse!
At least we're still warm and dry.
[thunder crashes]
Um, why was that rumble so ominous?
Something's headed our way.
[Beaver] No! It can't be.
Water!
Gotta rebuild the dam!
Hurray! That was close.
[yells, groans]
You better put these on.
[Beaver] Gosh darn it!
-[all screaming]
-No, no! No, no, no!
[Beaver cries]
[sighs] Who needs a bathtub
when there's an indoor swimming pool?
Truer words were never spoken, sister.
[chuckles]
I give these lodgings five stars!
Four, sister.
Housekeeping is not up to snuff.
-Really?
-Mm-hmm.
[laughs]
[sighs] So this is what it's like
to live under the sea.
I thought there'd be more dancing.
Um, it's not always better down
where it's wetter.
-Common misconception.
-[thunder crashes]
[both gasp]
[laughing]
Have you noticed that every time
thunder claps, something bad happens?
It can't get any worse than this!
[coughing]
I don't wanna jinx it...
Then please don't.
But that's got to be it, right?
Don't say it, Rapunzel.
-I mean, what else could go wrong?
-[Pascal trills]
-[thunder crashes]
-I wouldn't ask that out loud.
[squealing]
[Rapunzel] Oh, no.
[Cheshire Cat laughing]
[Magic Mirror mumbles]
[Rapunzel] What are those things?
Runaway foliage!
[Rapunzel] We have to save the animals!
[grunting]
[yelps]
[grunts]
Pua! [grunts]
I got you.
[yelps]
[grunting]
Close the windows!
-[grunts] Come on, Raj-- [screams]
-[Rajah growls]
Let's get you out of here.
[Rapunzel grunts]
[yells]
[screams]
[grunts]
I have no idea
how I'm brushing this mess out.
Thanks a lot, vines.
Oh, now this is a show. [laughs]
I'm so glad we caught the second half!
[laughs]
Yes, the drama! [chuckles]
[grunts] What do we do?
We need a sword!
Or a machete!
Or, oh! An axe!
Magic Mirror, can you help us?
[blowing] Yeah.
Skilled with tools is one you seek...
-[Magic Mirror speaks indistinctly]
-Magic Mirror?
I'm afraid there simply is no time
for dulcet tones or a poetic rhyme.
[Ariel] We need the Princess
here right quick,
-before the vines become too thick!
-[Heihei yelps]
Very well.
[disembodied voice breathing deeply]
Did someone call for an axe?
[laughing]
-Snow White!
-I knew you'd make it!
[giggles] Oh!
Huh?
Oh!
[Snow White] How did you get in there?
Well, it's off to work I go!
[grunts, chuckles]
[chuckles]
[growls]
[Heihei squawks]
[yells]
[Snow White chuckles, grunts]
[thumping]
[grunting]
[chuckling]
[straining]
[grunting]
[screaming]
No!
-No!
-Got caught up in the moment. [chuckles]
-So much hair.
Yes, I get it. I have a lot of hair.
Mm. Done.
-Yes!
-[sighs]
Where did this land seaweed come from?
[bird chirping]
This must have been some party.
We were having a quiet, rainy day indoors.
Then all of a sudden...
Bunnies. [grunts] Everywhere.
-Everywhere.
-How lucky!
And other creatures, too,
all coming in through the portals.
[sighs] But we're not sure why.
That's strange.
Let me ask our friend what she knows.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm!
Oh! She says she was invited.
-Invited?
-[thunder crashes]
[creaking]
The castle's going to collapse!
[grunts] We have to get the animals
out of here.
Before the ceiling caves in!
-But how?
-There's too many of them
and not enough of us!
[Mushu] Did I hear someone
ask for a miracle?
Let me hear ya say... [yelling] Ah!
[yelling] Ah!
That's close enough!
[gasps] Mushu!
[all chuckling]
-[laughter]
-Hurray!
I'm so glad to see you.
[chuckles] You know I'm always ready
to jump in and help you,
but we are gonna talk later
about you not invitin' me to this party,
'cause this looked epic!
[thunder crashes]
Hurry! Before we're all royal rubble!
Now let's make this cinematic!
-[narrator] Mushu!
-[laughing]
[screaming]
[Mushu chuckles]
All right, move it along!
Little guys in front.
[animal sounds]
Careful now. Don't trample the dragon.
[monkeys screeching]
[whistles]
[narrator] Carpet!
Rajah!
[Rajah roars]
[monkeys screeching]
Um, anyone down here?
[Pascal trills]
-[squeals]
-[narrator] Pascal!
[Pascal trilling]
[Rapunzel screaming]
Everybody out!
[clucks]
[narrator] Heihei!
[caws]
Pua!
[grunts, yells]
[growls]
-[Heihei caws]
-Nice bears?
-[Moana screaming]
-[Heihei clucking]
Not a great hair day!
[snakes hissing]
[narrator] Flounder!
[blows raspberry]
-[snakes hissing]
-Uh... Uh...
You can't get me! [laughs]
[Flunder laughing]
Wait.
Where's Snow White?
There's no time to lose.
You have to leave immediately!
Oh! Whoa!
[screaming]
[screaming continues]
-[grunts]
-[birds chirping]
Oh. How nice.
-[chuckles, gasps]
-[rumbling]
[rumbling]
[crashing]
Oh, goodness.
I can't believe it.
That's a lot of bricks.
[thud]
[sighs] Such a splendid holiday, Amelia.
[chuckles]
Oh, quite, Abigail.
Though a little more crowded
than I had expected for such a big castle.
-[Heihei caws]
-Oh!
Oh, dear.
Do you think we should come back?
-[Heihei clucks]
-[Amelia] Why not?
I do so love an exciting holiday.
[animal sounds]
[Rajah growls]
[grunts, gasps] Oh, oh!
[chuckles nervously]
[Mulan] Well...
Building with bricks is one of my favorite
rainy-day activities.
But why did this happen?
And why was there always a flash of pink
with every shift?
A flash of pink, you say?
Only one creature
could pull off a day like today, and...
[caws]
...punctuate it with that color.
[yelling] Cheshire Cat!
Ta-da! [chuckles] That's me.
-Are you hurt?
-A frayed whisker.
Nothing a little tea won't fix.
While you finish your tea,
maybe you can tell us
why you brought all these animals
into the castle?
-And the water?
-And the vines?
That was a bit much.
Now, now.
It was just a bit of rainy-day fun!
Rainy-day fun
doesn't destroy an entire castle.
Tell me, are you all mad?
Mad?
Steaming mad?
No, Cheshire Cat, we aren't mad.
Uh, actually...
[chuckles] I am a little mad.
But we are ready to rebuild.
And you're going to help us!
-[sighs]
-Would you like me to whistle?
While you work?
That won't be necessary.
[thunder crashes]
[laughing]
[clattering]
[vocalizing]
[chuckling]
[Wardrobe] Oh, for heaven's sake!
Would you look at that!
[Ariel] [chuckling]
It's even better than before!
[gasps] Come on, everyone!
Let's go check it out!
-[Jasmine] Yes!
-[Rapunzel] Amazing!
My work here is done. [sighs]
Now I'm bored.
Where to... [chuckling] next?
[princesses cheering and laughing]
[Jasmine] It's all so magical!
[Mulan] Oh, I love it.
-[Snow White] [gasps] How wonderful!
-[Moana] [chuckling] All right!
[Ariel] Oh, have you seen anything
so wonderful in your entire life?
[Rapunzel]
Nothing could possibly go wrong now.
[all] Rapunzel!
[theme music playing]